Whose idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?
是谁出主意 让服务生都穿溜冰鞋的？
Some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.
某个白痴客人投意见箱的
-Oh,my God! They took my idea! -That was you?
天哪，他们盗用我的想法 是你？
Okay,there you go.
过去吧
Rachel,I made you cocoa.
瑞秋，我帮你泡了可可
Oh,that's so....
小心…
Oh,my God! Are you guys okay?
天哪！你们还好吗？
Oh,my.
辣喔
The One With a Chick and a Duck
本集播出：“鸡同鸭讲”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
You know,with that goatee, you kind of look like Satan.
你留山羊胡有点像撒旦
So that's why the priest threw holy water on me.
所以神父才会对我沥圣水
You have to cheer up.
你得开心一点
You should come out with Ross and me.
你应该跟我和罗斯出门
Anything is better than sitting here crying all day about Kate.
总比整天坐着为凯特伤心好
I was crying because nobody believed Quincy's theory.
我伤心是因为 没有人相信昆西的理论
I'm gonna be on TV!
我要上电视了
No way!
不会吧
They're putting together a panel to talk about the fossils in Peru.
有一个讨论秘鲁化石的座谈会
The Discovery Channel's filming it!
探索频道要去拍摄
Oh,my God! Who's gonna watch that?
天哪！谁会看？
Thanks. You ready to go?
谢了，可以走了吗？
I saw a girl with that vest.
我看过一个女生穿那件背心
Thanks.
谢了
Most of us think of chocolate and baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
大部份的人都视巧克力和篮子 为传统的复活节礼物
Some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
有些人坚持送活的小鸡
Unfortunately,most of these guys won't live to see the 4th of July.
不幸的是，大部份的小鸡 都活不到国庆日
As a result of improper care, they will be dead.
由于照顾得不妥善 它们马上就会死
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
你们有小鸡吗？
I was watching this commercial on TV, and,man,those things are cute!
我看到电视上的广告 那些小鸡好可爱
Pete,you're back! Hey,check this out!
彼特，你回来了！你看
Skates!
溜冰鞋
You're sturdier than Chandler. He crumbled like a piece of paper.
你比钱德结实，他一撞就倒
How was your trip?
旅途顺利吗？
What'd you bring me?
你送什么给我？
Hotel toiletries from Japan!
日本饭店的化妆品
These are gonna go in my permanent collection.
我要永远保留下来
-Want some coffee? -That'd be great.
要喝咖啡吗？ 好啊
Regular or decaf?
普通还是低咖啡因？
Whichever's closest.
最近的就行了
-Ask me what I did today. -What did you do today?
问我今天做了什么 你今天做了什么？
I bought a restaurant and I'd like you to be the chef.
我买下一家餐厅 想请你当主厨
Can you believe he offered me a restaurant?
他居然要送我一家餐厅
What a jerk. You want me to kick his ass?
那个混蛋，你要我踹他吗？
It's been my dream since I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
从我拥有好烘烤箱 开了好吃糕饼店起
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
就在梦想这一天
I would kill for this job. I can totally do this job...
我死也甘愿，我绝对能胜任
...and God knows,I've paid my dues.
我吃的苦头也够多了
But Pete's doing this because he has a crush on me.
但彼特这么做是因为他喜欢我
And you're still not attracted to him at all?
你对他还是没兴趣？
How could I accept a restaurant from him? I can't.
我怎么能接下这个餐厅？ 我不能
I couldn't accept a necklace from Stu Vincent in the 7th grade.
七年级时史都文森 送我项链我也没收
But,Mon,that was totally different. He was your health teacher.
这是两回事 他是你的健康教育老师
What,honey?
怎么了？
My side hurts from when you crashed into me.
被你撞到的地方好痛
Oh,God,I'm so sorry.
天哪，对不起
Oh,God!
天哪
Hey,you guys. Guess what?
嗨，你们猜怎样？
Got a job on a riverboat?
你在邮轮上找到工作？
I didn't wear this suit for a year, because you hated it.
我一整年没穿这套西装 因为你不喜欢
You're not my girlfriend anymore,so....
你不是我的女朋友了，所以…
I see. This suit is making a point.
我懂了，你想要强调
Now that you're on your own,you're free to look as stupid as you'd like.
你现在孤家寡人 可以尽情的出丑
You like it,right?
你喜欢这套西装吧？
I like it even more on you than I did on Colonel Sanders.
当然，你穿起来 比肯德基爷爷好看
Ross,I'm kidding. Come here.
罗斯，开玩笑的，回来
What were you gonna tell us?
你要说什么？
Was it how you invented the cotton gin?
你发明轧棉机的过程？
So after you put the suggestion in the box...
你投书到意见箱之后
...how long did it take for it to happen?
多久才得到回应？
About three months.
大约三个月
So I guess that's about two weeks before the topless thing kicks in.
所以离上空的规定 大约还有两星期
I got you something. Open it! Open it!
我买了一个东西 打开来看
It's a chicken.
是一只鸡
It's cute,huh?
很可爱吧？
You guys? Do you know anything about chicks?
两位，你们了解鸡吗？
Fowl? No.
家禽？不了解
Women? No.
女人？不了解
They are a huge responsibility.
养鸡是重责大任
Especially at this age. They require constant care.
尤其是小鸡 需要无微不至的照顾
They need just the right food and lots and lots of love.
它们不能吃错东西 需要很多关爱
Well,no problem there.
这个没问题
Easy,Lenny.
轻一点，大母鸡
So,I mean,have you thought about it?
你考虑过了吗？
Okay,here's the thing.
是这样的
Not "the thing." I hate "the thing."
我讨厌“是这样的”
What's "the thing"?
是怎样的？
I can't do it.
我不能接受
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
抱歉，我也很想接受
... but you have these feelings for me.
但你对我有特殊情感
That's what you're worried about?
你在担心这个？
If that's the problem, we've got no problem.
如果是这个问题 那就没问题了
I was gonna tell you over dinner, but I met somebody else,on my trip.
我正打算吃饭时告诉你 我这趟出国认识了一个人
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist. We met on the plane.
她叫安，是记者 我们在飞机上认识
She wanted to finish off my peanuts.
她想把我的花生吃完
I thought she said something else. We had a big laugh.
我听成别的（花生音同阴茎） 我们大笑一场
I got tired of waiting.
我等烦了
That's great. I'm sorry, but I'm so happy for you.
太好了 抱歉，但我好为你高兴
-Now I can work for you! -I guess you can.
我可以为你工作了 看来可以了
Oh,my God! This is incredible!
天哪，太棒了
You know what? I'm gonna roll right into that office and quit!
你猜怎样？ 我要溜进办公室去辞职
All right!
好
Could you give me a little push?
推一下，好吗？
Good luck!
祝你好运
I'm quitting!
我要辞职了
I'm okay! I'm all right!
我没事，我很好
That's exciting. You went to Japan,made up a woman.
真叫人兴奋啊 你去日本，认识一个女人
What?
什么？
I'm just saying,this "woman," I mean,she's fictitious,no?
我是说这个女人… 是虚构的吧？
-Why would you say that? -You're still into Monica.
为什么这么说？ 你还是喜欢摩妮卡
You said there's somebody else so she'd work with you.
你谎称认识别人 好让她为你做事
If you spend time together, maybe something might happen.
相处久了，也许就会产生感情
You're good. You're good.
你真行
No,I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
我只是直觉准，还会通灵
It's a substantial gift.
很实在的天赋
Can you promise me that you won't tell her?
请答应我不要告诉她
Absolutely. I promise. Tell her what?
没问题，我答应你 告诉她什么？
Thanks a lot.
谢谢你
No,I'm serious. I'm intuitive,but my memory sucks.
我是褚的 我的直觉很准，但记性很差
Okay,but this is the last time.
好吧，但这是最后一次
With a chick-chick here And a chick-chick there
这里吱，那里吱
Here a chick,there a chick Everywhere a chick-chick
这里吱，那里吱 到处都在吱吱叫…
Chicken....
鸡…
How's she doing?
鸡妹妹好吗？
She?
妹妹？
Don't you think it's a she?
你不觉得是妹妹吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
I can't tell. Whatever it was went back in too quickly.
看不出来，那个东西 一下子就缩回去了
I gotta change. I'm meeting some of the cast for drinks.
我要换衣服 我要去跟其他演员喝酒
Excuse me?
什么？
What?
怎么了？
I stayed home while you were at rehearsal...
你排练时，我留在家里
...so somebody could be here with our chick.
好陪着我们的小鸡
Who was up from 2:00 this morning until 5:00...
是谁从半夜两点撑到五点？
...trying to get her back to sleep?
好哄她睡觉？
You don't think I get up when you get up?
你以为我没起来吗？
Oh,here it comes.
又来了
Yes! Here it comes! I'm stuck here all day!
没错，又来了 我整天困在这里
And then you come in and spend two seconds with us...
你才回来陪了我们几秒钟
...and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends?
就要出去跟朋友花天酒地？
Well,I don't think so,mister!
这样不行喔，先生
I need to relax,okay? I was working all day.
我需要轻松一下 我忙了一整天
And you don't think taking care of our chick is work?
照顾我们的小鸡就不忙？
That's not what I said. I just meant
我不是那个意思，我是说…
I know what you meant!
我知道你想说什么
Did you notice that ever since we got this chick...
你有没有发现，自从有了小鸡
...we've been fighting a lot more than we used to?
我们争吵的次数变多了？
I don't know,maybe we weren't ready to have a chick.
也许我们还不适合养小鸡
I'll take her back tomorrow.
我明天送它回去
We'll get our $3 back?
三块钱会退吗？
I have that TV thing in two hours, and I need your help.
我两小时后要录影 请你们帮个忙
What do you think? This blue suit or this brown one?
怎么样？蓝色还是棕色的好？
The brown one brings out your eyes.
棕色可以突显你的眼睛
But your butt looks great in the blue one.
但蓝色那套让你的屁股很翘
Really?
真的？
That aspirin dance really works.
祈药舞还真有效
-ls that still...? -I'm fine.
你还是… 我没事
-No,you're not! -Yes,I am.
你有事 我没事
Look,I'm fine. Watch. Look at that.
我很好，看我的
You've got to go to a doctor,okay?
你得去看医生，好吗？
I have to get ready and go to a dinner at my boss's house.
我要去我老板家参加晚宴
There's people there that I have to meet.
有几个人非见不可
I'm sure you'll make a great impression. "Hi,I'm Rachel.
你一定会令人印象深刻 “你好，我是瑞秋”
It's nice to meet you."
“很高兴认识你”
Come on,you probably have a broken rib.
你的肋骨可能断了
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow. It'll still be broken then.
我明天再去医院，它还是断的
But you know,I could use a hand getting ready.
但我打扮时需要帮忙
Either help me,or go.
你不帮忙就走
Fine. I'll go.
好，我走
But before you go, could you help me first?
走之前能不能先帮忙？
Sure. I'll help you.
好，我帮
Good! Do you guys know how to get a chick out of a VCR?
你们在要怎么把小鸡 弄出录影机？
You know what? I cannot do this with my left hand.
你知道吗？我不会用左手化
Would you please help me with this too?
你能不能也帮我化妆？
Let's use this brush.
用这一支好了
-This stuff? -Careful.
这个？ 小心一点
Light.
沾一点
Just sweep it across the lid. Just sweep it.
在眼睑上刷一下就好 刷一下
Sorry!
对不起
That's just poking me in the eye.
你是在戳我的眼睛
I'm sorry. Close....
对不起，闭上…
-Just sweep it. -I'm sweeping.
刷一下就好 我在刷
Sweep,sweep....
刷、刷…
Now make it even, because we don't....
刷均匀，不要…
I don't want it to be too much. I want it to be subtle.
不要太多，隐隐约约就好
You don't wear enough of this.
你的妆不够浓
Since when do you think I don't wear enough of this?
你几时觉得我的妆不够浓了？
Close your eye. You're gonna like this better....
闭上眼睛，你一定会喜欢
-Close,close. -Blow it.
闭眼睛 吹一下
Because I think this will make you a little more sophisticated.
这样看起来比较世故、成熟
Sophisticated like a hooker?
跟妓女一样世故？
-Guess what I'm doing tonight. -What?
你猜我今晚要做什么？ 什么？
I'm checking out the restaurant with Pete.
我要跟彼特去看餐厅
Monica,I am so excited for you!
摩妮卡，我好替你兴奋
I have to tell you something.
我有一件事要告诉你
What?
什么事？
I can't tell you.
我不能告诉你
Wouldn't it be easier to tell me something that you could tell me?
把不能说的事说出来 不是会比较舒坦？
Well,sure,in a perfect world.
哪有那么好的事
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell, and I swore to all my Gods.
我答应不说 我对所有神明发过誓
Does it have to do with Ross and Rachel?
跟罗斯和瑞秋有关吗？
Does it have to do with Joey?
跟乔伊有关吗？
Does it have to do with Chandler and that sock he keeps by his bed?
跟钱德和他 床边的袜子有关吗？
No,but let's come back to that later.
不是，不过你待会儿要告诉我
There you go! Good enough for your party?
好了，够美了吧？
Sure.
是啊
Sure. I'll just sit next to the transsexual from purchasing.
是啊，我会坐在 采购部那个人妖旁边
All right,I gotta go, So good luck at the party.
我得走了，祝你晚宴愉快
Could you just stay and help me get dressed?
再帮我换一下衣服？
Sure.
当然好
Great. Okay,just turn around.
太好了，转过去吧
What?
什么？
I don't want you to see me naked.
我不想让你看到我的身体
I've seen you naked a million times. I ate hot fudge off you naked.
我看过几万遍了 我在你身上吃热奶油
I sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your bellybutton.
我从你的肚脐眼吸出小软糖
Yeah,but that was different. We were going out then.
那个不一样，我们那时在交往
Now it's weird.
现在很奇怪
Rach,you know,I can see you naked anytime I want.
我随时都能看到你的裸体
What?
什么？
All I have to do is close my eyes. See?
我只需要闭上眼睛，你看
Ross,stop that!
罗斯，别闹了
Come on! Don't think of me like that anymore.
拜托，别再那样想我了
Sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
抱歉，你管不到
It's one of my rights as the ex-boyfriend.
这是前任男友的权利
Stop it! Cut it out! Cut it out!
别闹了，够了
I'm sorry. It will never happen
对不起，我不会再…
Wait a minute! Wait,wait....
等一下
Now there are 100 of you, and I'm the king!
现在有一百个你，我是国王
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
成熟一点，这又没什么
All right. Fine.
好吧
See what you did? I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
很好，我决定自己换衣服
Oh,my God. All right,look,look....
天哪，听我说
Easy. Easy. You have to go to the hospital,okay?
小心，你得去医院，好吗？
I do. I really do.
我真的得去了
I'll get your coat, then I'll put you in a cab.
我去帮你拿外套，再送你上车
You're not gonna come with me?
你不陪我去吗？
Of course I am.
当然要
I just have to make a call.
我得先打个电话
Thank you.
谢谢
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I'm sorry. I just can't go to the hospital looking like this.
对不起，我不能这样去医院
Does it involve travel?
跟旅行有关吗？
Does it involve clogs?
跟木屐有关吗？
Clogs or claws?
木屐还是爪子？
Clogs.
木屐
Claws?
爪子？
So it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel or Chandler or Joey.
所以不是罗斯和瑞秋 也不是钱德和乔伊
What about Pete?
那彼特呢？
What is it?
怎么样？
-What about Pete? -I don't know!
彼特怎么了？ 我不知道
I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
我好像在跟灵犬莱西说话
-Phoebe,would you just tell me? -I can't!
菲比，你就直说好吗？ 不行啦
-I gotta go. -But you're so close!
我得走了 但是很接近了
Something to do with Pete's company?
跟彼特的电脑公司有关吗？
Go! You'll never get it!
你走吧，你死也猜不到的
I know.
我知道
See,yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
没错，那就是雅丝敏布丽丝
She's a completely different kind of chick.
她是一种完全不同的“鸡”
I love you both.
你们两个我都爱
But in very different ways.
是非常不一样的爱
What are you doing? You were gonna take her back.
你在干什么？不是要送她走？
I did. But the store wouldn't take her back.
我有，但是店里不收
Then I took her to the shelter. You know what I found out?
我带她去收容所 你猜我发现什么？
If they can't find a home for her, they kill her!
要是找不到人领养 就要杀了她
I won't let that happen to little Jasmine.
我绝不让小雅丝敏惨遭毒手
Good,good,because I was kind of having second thoughts too.
很好，其实我也有点反悔
And it's not just chicks. It's all kinds of other animals.
不只小鸡，所有的动物都一样
That's horrible. You did the right thing.
太可怕了，你做得对
Thanks. I'm glad you see it that way.
谢了，你这么想就好
Funny story!
说来好笑
I don't believe this!
真不敢相信
Look at this refrigerator! It's gigantic!
你看这个冰柜，有够大的
I could live in this thing! I'd be cold,but I'm always cold!
我可以住在里面 会冷，不过我本来就很冷
Oh,my God! Look at these spider burners! I love spider burners!
是传统火炉 我最喜欢传统火炉了
So you like it?
你喜欢罗？
It is so perfect! Thank you so much.
太完美了，真谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
Did you just smell my hair?
你刚才在闻我的头发？
No! No way! What?
怎么可能，没有啊
-Oh,God. -What?
天哪 怎么了？
You still have feelings for me.
你对我还是有感觉
I'm just excited about the restaurant, that's all.
我只是对餐厅的事很兴奋
I love you. Is that so bad?
我爱你，有这么糟吗？
No,it's not bad. It's not bad at all.
不糟，一点也不糟
It's really nice.
其实很好
The only one who stands to get hurt is me,and I'm okay with that.
会受伤的人是我 我都不介意了
You may be okay with getting hurt...
你或许不介意受伤
...but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you.
我却不能当那个伤你的人
That's why I can't take this job.
所以我不能接受这份工作
What?
什么？
We probably shouldn't see each other anymore.
我们也不该再见面了
I'm sorry.
对不起
I mean,if that's really what you want,okay.
你如果真的这么想，那好吧
I'm sorry things
很抱歉事情…
Shut up for a second and let me just see something.
你先闭嘴，让我确认一下
You'd tell me the truth?
你有说实话吗？
Rach,you can't look fat in an x-ray.
X光片看起来怎么会胖
Now you stay out here and you think about what you did!
你给我在这里好好反省
-That's a duck! -That's a bad duck!
那是一只鸭子 一只坏鸭子
How'd the thing go tonight,Ross?
今晚的事顺利吗？
What thing? What thing?
什么事？
Nothing. There was this thing at the museum. Come on.
没什么，博物馆有事 走吧
Easy.
小心
Now,when you come back,I hope you remember that that chick is not a toy!
等你回来，请记住 小鸡不是玩具
What "thing"? What is this "thing"?
到底是什么事？
I was kind of supposed to be on TV tonight for the Discovery Channel.
我今晚本来要上探索频道
Oh,my God!
天哪
Ross,why didn't you tell me that?
罗斯，你为什么不说？
I knew that if I told you, you'd make me go...
我一说，你就会逼我去
...and I knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. Come on.
我知道你今晚 需要有人陪着，来吧
-I cannot believe you. -What?
我真不敢相信 怎么了？
That is the sweetest thing.
你对我太好了
You should get some sleep.
你该睡觉了
Sorry I spoiled your evening.
抱歉搞砸你的计划
As long as you're okay.
你没事就好
So I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见
See you.
再见
What did you do?
你犯了什么错？
What you doing?
你们在干什么？
Having a swim.
游泳
What about the chick?
小鸡呢？
Chicks don't swim.
鸡不会游泳
Are you sure?
确定？
I don't know.
不晓得
-Should we try? -Sure.
要试试看吗？ 好啊
See,I told you. They don't swim.
看吧，我就说它不会游
Well,give him a minute.
再等一下
It's okay. It's okay,baby,baby,baby.
乖，没事了